请醒来。
鸟...
你在说什么？
鸟！我看到一只鸟！
鸟？ 怎么了？
这是怎么回事？
梦的世界 3
请提防戈林的。
许多战争纽曼的已经下降到你的世界
和你在一起。
瞳...
真是病房守护神降体。
但是，我该怎么办？
寻找其他病房号码？
要问他们一个接一个？
和...
请记住...
你的力量源自
爱与被爱。
你是爱的战士。
当你发现你失去爱人，
你会比别人强。
要开启爱与被爱实力？
你的意思是
我应该爱我所有的女孩？
什么，你这是什么表情？
我很佩服你有这么多的空闲时间。
但是，我必须找出
病房数下降到这个城市。
你知道什么是病房的守护神？
这是不可能知道的。
你想让我和你一起去？
你要去哪里？
双叶，没必要装了。
你不喜欢他吗？
是的...
你是什么意思是？
我每一次我见到他都和他吵架。
而且似乎他喜欢别的女孩。
也许我...我还不如那些女孩。
但是你拒绝。
事实上，你害怕被抛弃和伤害。
所以，你找理由逃避你的感受。
这是正确的，也许是。
现在双叶应该勇敢。
要勇敢？
欢迎！
下午好，隈研。
呀！
这是你的店？
我在这里工作。
因为我喜欢非常动物。
在这里，
我能更接近这些小动物。
似乎很久很久以前，
我住在一起，很多动物。
但是，你觉得我很狡猾？
保卫这些动物...
说我喜欢动物
我不得不这样做。
这是这个世界的规则。
谁了这些制定的规则？
对不起，我不怪你。
我知道。
我有时做梦。
做梦？
关于美丽的森林。
在这个世界上...
动物和人的自由生活。
而你也是我的梦想。
我？
看来我们之前见过。
在我们见面的第一次，
你和我...
和你...
似乎我们很久很久以前是朋友。
我也是。
真的吗？
也许...
我们有同样的梦想。
梦想？
米娅。
你知道什么是病房的守护神？
沃德守护神？
这是什么？
你不知道吗？
不，谢了。
关于你刚才提到的梦想，
关于梦想是什么？
我不记得清楚。
在梦中......
我想...
我们必须...
成为男女朋友。
然后...
那只是一个梦。
但我真的很喜欢你。
我也喜欢你。
米娅，是它好吗？
我决定给你我的童贞。
现在？
怎么了？
No.
什么也没有。
双叶！
你为什么在这里？
双叶，等待！
米娅，对不起。
我下次再来。
为什么，为什么呀？
为什么，为什么瞳？
为什么不是我？
Neika老师。
感觉好些吗？
是的，对不起，给您添麻烦了。
没问题，不要放在心里。
这里有一些咖啡。
谢谢，不客气了。
那个很美吧?
是的...
但是
性爱是爱情的歌制成的血肉。
重复波动快感的巅峰。
在燃烧快乐，
我已经获得了高潮很多次。
对，这就像传说中的凤凰。
性爱很伟大。
难道你不这么认为吗？
我不太清楚。
但是你想要知道，对不对？
双叶，老师知道你非常好。
我知道你觉得很孤独。
老师希望你能忘记他。
给你一个甜美的梦。
不!
老师，请停下来！
请住手！
你真的要我停下来？
好吧，我会停下来呢。
不要！不要停。
那么你是不是应该求我？
求你.
我求求你，请你继续。
你说你会服从我的所有要求。
我会按照老的要求来做的
好。既然你这么强烈，双叶。
这真的很难拒绝。
什么？
What's the matter with you?
Isn't it your important member?
This is something of a man.
Why... on my body?
No need for you to fear, Futaba.
This is only a dream.
Dream?
Right, you are now in dream.
In the dream, you are a ward numen
who have two sexual characters.
Miya.
In the dream, you can spread your love freely...
with men and women you loved.
Well...
I want it.
Is it very good?
OK, open black wing.
Fly with your desire.
I'm coming.
Oh, yeah.
It's just like this, do it at your own will.
It's a compensation for the love
you didn't get from Aoterubu.
Aoterubu
Love...
I have decided...
to give Aoterubu my virginity.
It has been late before we know it.
Sorry to keep you wating.
Mia.
Kengo, what's going on?
This late.
but I care for one thing at all time.
but you can call me.
I don't have your number.
And I want to see you too.
Mia, can you tell me the dream in details
which you mentioned to me earlier?
That dream?
What's wrong with that dream?
I hope you can remember it carefully.
To me. No, to us.
that is very important.
It is so...
Wait a minute.
Kengo.
Stop, Aoterubu.
You can't bully a friend.
What are you saying?
Please look carefully.
Futaba?! Futaba, is it you?
Right.
But her looks... could it...
That woman was a ward numen in her last life too.
She can't get your love.
so she turned to be a night ghost with to much sorrow.
It also means...
the one who made her to be a night ghost...
is you, Aoterubu.
Can't get my love?
Forgive me, Futaba.
It's all because of me not noticing your love.
Mia.
No, no.
You must do it with me.
You'll enjoy the happiness, Aoterubu.
Let me go!
Does it taste good?
It is effective to both man and woman.
What?
Look.
You're so energized.
Stop!
Shido.
Stop.
Futaba!
Miya.
If it wasn't for you,
Aoterubu would have loved me.
Aoterubu is mine!
Aoterubu...
Wonderful, wonderful.
Get it?
It's time to get your love strength.
You...
I see.
You are not the real Aoterubu.
What do you mean?
I have remembered.
tyat I was the ward numen in dream world.
Lusano's forest, Miyu.
So Mia is Miyu.
Well, it's too good.
Miyu.
Futaba, Futaba.
Are you OK?
Kengo.
Mia.
Sorry, Mia.
Sorry I have done the wrong thing to you.
No problem, this is not your fault.
Yes, don't mind.
Thank you...
Kengo.
Are you willing to love me?
I'll love you.
I love you now.
Me too.
That woman said something strange.
You are not the true Aoterubu.
What did she mean?
And...
Who is that man?